<list>
  <singleArtist>
    <id>1</id>
    <recordLabel/>
    <typeOfArtist>SINGLE_ARTIST</typeOfArtist>
    <biography>Elizaveta Gyrdymova was born on 1 June 1998 in Yekaterinburg. From childhood, Gyrdymova enjoyed writing poetry and published her work on the site Stihi.ru as a teenager.[1]  In 2014, she entered tenth grade at the Specialized Educational and Scientific Center of the Ural Federal University.[2] In 2016, she enrolled in correspondence courses in film production at the Gerasimov Institute of Cinematography in Moscow. She chose the school because of her love of classic cinema.[3]  Since September 2016, Gyrdymova has continued her studies, and her first internship was at the ETV channel in her native Yekaterinburg, where she released joint projects with the poet Alexandra Aksyonova.[4] She then worked for some time as a producer at ETV.[1]  In May 2022, it became known that the singer left Russia for Lithuania.[5]  In January 2023, the Russian Ministry of Justice included Gyrdymova in the list of foreign agents.[6][7]</biography>
    <picture>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monetochka#/media/File:Монеточка_(концерт_Монеточки_в_А2)_2019_(cropped).jpg</picture>
    <name>Monetochka</name>
    <memberships/>
  </singleArtist>
  <bend>
    <id>2</id>
    <recordLabel/>
    <typeOfArtist>BAND</typeOfArtist>
    <name>Depeche Mode</name>
    <description>Pioneering English band Depeche Mode took the underground electronic club sounds of the early &apos;80s and expanded them to stadium-sized levels within a decade, becoming one of the best-selling international groups in the process. One of the first acts to establish a musical identity based completely around the use of synthesizers, they debuted with a bouncy electro-pop spirit which gradually developed into a darker, more dramatic synth-rock style that ultimately positioned them as one of the most quintessential alternative bands of their era. Earning a modest European following with early releases like 1981&apos;s Speak &amp; Spell and 1983&apos;s Construction Time Again, they made their U.S. breakthrough in 1984 with their platinum-certified fourth LP, Some Great Reward. From there, Depeche Mode remained a fixture on the international Top Ten with hit &apos;90s albums such as the classic Violator and their first U.S./U.K. number one, the grunge-influenced Songs of Faith and Devotion. While internal drama and struggles with substance abuse threatened to derail them by the late &apos;90s, their ever-evolving sound adapted with the times, whether diving into moody trip-hop on 1997&apos;s Ultra or digitizing with experimental electronic on 2001&apos;s Exciter. By the late 2000s, the trio experienced a popular resurgence and renewed drive with the chart-topping electro-rock Playing the Angel, which kicked off a new era that poised Depeche Mode as elder statesmen of the genre, dominating sales with each subsequent release and even embarking on their longest tour to date, in support of their 14th album, 2017&apos;s politically charged Spirit. Major changes carried them into the 2020s: after they were inducted into the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame during the COVID-19 pandemic, they were reduced to a duo following the death of founding member Andy &quot;Fletch&quot; Fletcher in 2022. The next year, they processed the years of losses on the contemplative Memento Mori...</description>
    <dateOfEstablishment>1980-10-10</dateOfEstablishment>
    <memberships/>
  </bend>
  <singleArtist>
    <id>3</id>
    <recordLabel/>
    <typeOfArtist>SINGLE_ARTIST</typeOfArtist>
    <biography>Artiste multi-récompensé à la tête de plus de 6 millions d’albums vendus.    Génie de la musique, à tout juste 36 ans, GIMS est déjà à l&apos;origine d’un nombre incalculable de tubes : &quot;Bella&quot;, &quot;J&apos;me tire&quot;, &quot;Est-ce que tu m&apos;aimes&quot;, &quot;Zombie&quot;, &quot;Je te pardonne&quot;, &quot;Tout donner&quot;, &quot;Mi Gna&quot;, &quot;Corazon&quot; ou encore l&apos;incontournable &quot;Sapés comme jamais&quot;, pour lequel il reçoit une Victoire de la musique en 2016 et qui bat tous les records d’écoute. Sans oublier &quot;La même (en duo avec Vianney)&quot;, chanson francophone la plus diffusée en radio depuis 15 ans.  Caché derrière ses célèbres lunettes noires, GIMS est un artiste et showman hors normes.  Il est le premier rappeur francophone à remplir le Stade de France.</biography>
    <picture>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f6/Maître_Gims_Cannes_2016.jpg</picture>
    <name>GIMS</name>
    <memberships/>
  </singleArtist>
  <singleArtist>
    <id>4</id>
    <recordLabel/>
    <typeOfArtist>SINGLE_ARTIST</typeOfArtist>
    <biography>Billie Eilish remains one of the biggest stars to emerge in the 21st century. Her third studio album, HIT ME HARD AND SOFT features 10 tracks written and recorded in her hometown of Los Angeles, with her brother and producer FINNEAS. In 2019, her debut album WHEN WE ALL FALL ASLEEP, WHERE DO WE GO? debuted at No. 1 in 18 countries, and was the most streamed album of that year. In 2021, her sophomore album &apos;Happier Than Ever’ debuted at #1 in 20 countries. Both albums were critically acclaimed worldwide and were written, produced, and recorded entirely by Billie Eilish and FINNEAS. 9-time GRAMMY® Award-winning Billie Eilish has made history as the youngest artist to receive nominations and win in all the major GRAMMY® categories, receiving an award for Best New Artist, Album of the Year, Record of the Year, Song of the Year, and Best Pop Vocal Album, and is the youngest artist to write and record an official James Bond theme song, ‘No Time To Die,’ which won an Academy Award for Best Original Song in 2022. In 2023, Eilish also wrote and released the critically acclaimed song “What Was I Made For?” for the Greta Gerwig-directed motion picture Barbie, which also won Academy and Golden Globe Award for Best Original Song, two GRAMMY® Awards for Song of the Year and Best Song Written For Visual Media, and has solidified Billie Eilish yet again in the history books as the youngest person ever to win two Academy Awards.</biography>
    <picture>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Billie_Eilish_Vogue_2023.jpg</picture>
    <name>Billie Eilish</name>
    <memberships/>
  </singleArtist>
</list>